# MARK AKSELROD

Cell Phone: (415) 845-6865 Email: makselrod50@gmail.com

#### **KEY SKILLS**

**Networking and LAN Systems Professional** 

**Experience with Microsoft** Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint, & Outlook

Linux and iOS Knowledge and Comprehension

**Informed on Developing** Marketing & Social Media Strategies/Trends

> Fluent in Russian, Intermediate level in Spanish, Speak and **Understand Hebrew**

**Analytical Thinker & Situational Problem Solver** 

**Administrative and Office** Experience

**Work Well Under Pressure** 

#### **EDUCATION**

California State University, Chico, Class of 2009

**Bachelors of Science in Business Administration** 

**Option in Organizational** Management

**Minor in International Business** 

**CA Real Estate Broker** License #01895862 (Exp.)

**International Military** Experience

## IT & MANAGEMENT PROFESSIONAL

Information Technology position based in San Francisco or regional position involving some travel.

### CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

Hill & Co. Property Management: San Francisco, CA (2019-2020): IT Manager/Portfolio Manager including Rental Units and HOA Management. Oversaw all computer troubleshooting and installation for entire 2<sup>nd</sup> floor. Coordinated licensed and insured vendors along with ensuring strong tenant and owner relationships. Created budgets and oversaw upcoming projects along with taking care of any deferred maintenance. Overhauled and Upgraded all Project Management Systems. Assisted in creating Cloud Systems and Digital Communication Upgrades. Laid-off due to Corona Virus (COVID-19 Outbreak March 13<sup>th</sup>, 2020). letters of recommendation available upon request.

Property Management One: San Francisco, CA (2018-2019): IT Support & HOA manager responsible for all Windows related troubleshooting and continued projects that were stalled by coordinating with new vendors and implementing new strategies. Projects included Seismic Retrofits, Full unit Remodeling, Mold Remediation, and Deferred Maintenance.

Golden Gate Properties: San Francisco, CA (2016-2017): Redid entire Appfolio database for owner/tenant/vendor collaboration and immediate maintenance request response capability. Continued to improve vendor/owner/tenant procedures and standard operating procedures.

Property Manager and Real Estate Advisor: San Francisco, CA (2014-2016): Ran a portfolio of 15 rental properties in San Francisco and Daly City for multiple owners. Installed the video camera and router framework for 12 properties. Created property management software for all owners to collaborate on one system. Provided all vendor recommendations, ran all day-to-day operations including finances, tenant relations, and suggested/procured new project development for all properties. Properties ranged from 2 to 11 units.

Prime Asset Management: San Diego, CA (2009-2014): Operations manager and head of IT department; oversaw marketing, development and overall business reconciliation. Remade entire networking system and connected all the vendors and managers on one secure structure. Worked in tandem with vendors and owners on large multi-family real estate projects in San Diego.